<Patch>
    <Operation Class="VFECore.PatchOperationToggableSequence">
        <enabled>True</enabled>
        <label>[Erin's Shisune] rework shisune to use AFU cosmetics</label>
        <operations>
            <li Class="PatchOperationRemove">
                <xpath>//XenotypeDef[defName="ERN_Shisune"]/genes/li[text()="ERN_ShisuneHead" or text()="ERN_ShisuneEars_Classic" or text()="ERN_ShisuneEars_Droopy" or text()="ERN_ShisuneEars_Fluffy" or text()="ERN_ShisuneEars_Floppy" or text()="ERN_ShisuneEars_Long" or text()="ERN_ShisuneEars_Round" or text()="ERN_ShisuneTail_ClassicFox" or text()="ERN_ShisuneTail_Cloudy" or text()="ERN_ShisuneTail_Tri" or text()="ERN_ShisuneAntlers_Branch" or text()="ERN_ShisuneAntlers_Twig" or text()="ERN_ShisuneAntlers_Sprig"]</xpath>
            </li>
            <li Class="PatchOperationAdd">
                <xpath>//XenotypeDef[defName="ERN_Shisune"]/genes</xpath>
                <value>
                    <li>AFU_HA_FoxEar</li>
                    <li>AFU_BA_FoxTail</li>
                </value>
            </li>
            <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
                <xpath>//XenotypeDef[defName="ERN_Shisune"]/description</xpath>
                <value>
                    <description>An unusual xenotype with vulpes genes, shisune are social humans that wish to live simpler lives amongst nature. More in tune with their instincts, they enjoy the presence of others, sometimes carnally, and are adept hunters of small game under moonlight. Their reactionary behaviour can be somewhat detrimental as they can assume parts of their own body as prey.\n\nBased on a completely mythical retelling of fox-people found in ancient Terran pop culture, the vast majority of shisune tend to live on planets with a high ratio of non-urbanized landmass. They have proven quite popular with small-scale farmlands who try to rely less on technology developed by megacorporations.\n\nDue to awakened dormant hibernator genes in the xenogerm, shisune tend to keep to their personal dwellings during the winter months but are far more active than baseliners during the summer periods.</description>
                </value>
            </li>
            <li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
                <xpath>//XenotypeDef[defName="ERN_Shisune"]/descriptionShort</xpath>
                <value>
                    <descriptionShort>An unusual xenotype with vulpes genes, shisune are social humans that wish to live simpler lives amongst nature. More in tune with their instincts, they enjoy the presence of others, sometimes carnally, and are adept hunters of small game under moonlight.</descriptionShort>
                </value>
            </li>
        </operations>
    </Operation>
</Patch>